Pulak Debasish Prusty

I'm a final year B.Tech student having a great interest in Android Development. I'm currently working on a music player app to release on Play Store. I started learning all by myself and soon entered freelancing and completed 3 small projects which gave me an important experience I needed. I have been a mentor for Android and Java courses at Internshala as part of my internship. I have a strong grit to learn and develop my skills while working with like-minded people in collaboration.



pulakdebasish@gmail.com

Bhubaneswar, Odisha

pulakdp.github.io

+917008980991

in linkedin.com/in/pulakdebasish

stackoverflow.com/users/6200183/pulak

EDUCATION

B.Tech

College of Engineering and Technology, Bhubaneswar

08/2014 - Present

CGPA: 8.14/10

Stream:

 Computer Science and Engineering

Intermediate

Kendriya Vidyalaya, Puri

2012 - 2014

Percentage: 92.8%

WORK EXPERIENCE

Intern - Java & Android Course Mentor Internshala

06/2017 - 10/2017

Tasks

- Answering forum queries for Java and Android training courses
- Live Chat with students regarding their queries

Freelance Android App Developer Freelancer

02/2017 - 05/2017

Profile: www.freelancer.com/hireme/pulakprusty

Tasks/Achievements

Successfully completed 3 projects

SKILLS & COMPETENCES

Android

Java

C++

SQL

Kotlin

Python

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Flair Music Player app(Work in progress)

 Android App - Simple yet intuitive music player that's a joy to look at and use

Personal Notes App

 Android App - A notes app that allows users to save images and have the notes synced with Google Drive and Dropbox

Popular Movies

 Android App - To browse and view popular and top rated movies along with their details, ratings and video links

CERTIFICATES

Learn Android App Development With Java (12/2016 – 02/2017)

Certificate of Completion

Certificate of Internship (06/2017 – 10/2017)

Certificate for successful completion of Internship

LANGUAGES

INTERESTS

Technology

Football

Chess

Video Games

Crime Novels